#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

# For communication

- ✓ 12xushnudbek34@gmail.com
- Buxoro viloyati. Vobkent tumani
- **&** (99) 882-06-41
- https://github.com/xushnud123
- https://xushnudbek-raimov.vercel.app/

#### Profile

Hello, My name is Khushnudbek, I started programming in 2020. Speaking of skills, I have worked as a Frontend developer in 2 big projects so far. I have mastered several new technologies as a freelance graphic designer. I intend to master more technologies in the future and have made several plans

#### Skills

- Figma
- React js
- O HTML
- Next js
- o CSS, SCSS
- React Hooks
- UI frameworks
- Experience with React libraries
- TypeScript
- Redux , Redux Toolkit
- Astro js
- React Query

### Education

# 2019 - 2023 Tashkent University of Information Technologies

Toshkent

Faculty of Audiovisual Technologies, GPA: 4.1/5.0

## **Employment**

#### 2021-2023+ Comfi Payments

Comfi.app

BAA, DUBAI

I have been working at Comfi Payments for 1 year. I gained a lot of experience during my work. I learned React + TypeScript, Next + TypeScript, StoryBook, ReactQuery, organizing the SEO part, most importantly organizing Code Structure

2020- 2021 **Famic** 

Famic.io

BAA, DUBAI

I worked at Famic.io in the early years of my career. I participated in the construction of a project based on React js + Typescript in the company.

2020- 2021 **BFS** 

https://bfs.vercel.app/

UZBEKISTAN, Toshkent

I worked at Famic.io in the early years of my career. I participated in the construction of a project based on React js + Typescript in the company.